

Anjana Kanzariya

Backend Developer

My Contact

anjanajkanzariya@gmail.com

+91 9978910077

Rajkot, Gujarat, India

anjana-kanzariya.github.io

Core Skills

- Wordpress
- HTML & CSS
- PHP, C#, LINQ
- MS SQL & MySql
- · Javascript & jQuery
- Google Analytics & Tag Manager
- Data structures & Algorithms
- Shopify
- ASP.Net
- Photoshop

Soft Skills

- Observation
- Communication
- · Multi-tasking
- Learn new skills & Technology

Education

- Lukhdhirji Engineering College, Morbi Bachelor of Engineering - Information Technology - 2011
 Gold Medalist of 2011 batch
- Higher Secondary Education
 Kendriya Vidyalaya, Dhrangadhra 2007
 Scored 96 in Mathematics

About Me

Managing IT needs of a Design firm (UDLAB) for the past 7 years. Key skills include website design & development, database development and management, content creation and handling all the technical aspects of a website. Love to learn new skills and take initiative.

Professional Experience

Codeable, Denmark | Wordpress Expert 2022 - Present

• Codeabe certified WordPress expert

Universal Designovation Lab, India-USA | IT Specialist

2015 - Present

- Responsible for everything from domain, design & development to analytics, Pixel & ad tracking of the website.
- Create content for various projects & websites

Websmith Solution, Rajkot | Programmer 2014 - 2015

- Worked on API updation and database management
- Learnt & developed a Windows phone app that showed real-time MCX price changes

Department of Computer Science | Assistant Professor 2012 – 2013

Darshan Institute of Engineering & Technology, Rajkot

Subjects - Cloud Computing, Information Security, C# practicals

Department of CS & IT | Assistant Professor 2012

Om Shanti Engineering College, Rajkot

 Subjects - Operating System, Data Structures, SQL Practicals

Achievements

2022	Codeable certified Wordpress expert
2009	Won Spellathon competition